<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<message_catalog package_key="proctoring-support" locale="en_US" charset="ISO-8859-1">

  <msg key="accept">Accept</msg>
  <msg key="accept_message">An automated exam-supervision is activated to detect any fraudulent examination performance. You, your screen and your microphone will be recorded. Your data will only be used for the stated purpose, will be stored securely and will not be passed on to third parties.</msg>
  <msg key="audio_grabbing_not_supported">You are working with a browser that does not support the automated exam-supervision. Please use the latest version of Google &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.google.com/chrome/&#39;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;.</msg>
  <msg key="banner_message">The examination mode is activated. Close your browser window after the exam.</msg>
  <msg key="camera_cannot_be_recorded_because">Camera cannot be recorded. The error is:</msg>
  <msg key="camera_grabbing_not_supported">You are working with a browser that does not support the automated exam-supervision. Please use the latest version of Google &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.google.com/chrome/&#39;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;.</msg>
  <msg key="camera_not_found">No camera was recognized. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is not selected in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Camera\&#34; and select the correct camera.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is already being used by another program&lt;/b&gt;: Check whether the camera is currently running in another application (e.g. MS Teams). (Windows) Go to \&#34;Camera\&#34; | \&#34;Desktop apps\&#34; and check which desktop apps are currently using the camera. If desktop apps are currently accessing the camera, stop camera recording in those applications.(macOS) Check that there is a light next to the built-in camera. If so, restart the computer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;There is no camera&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the device manager and check whether a camera is displayed under \&#34;Image devices\&#34;, \&#34;Camera\&#34; or \&#34;Integrated camera\&#34;. (macOS) Under \&#34;System Settings\&#34; go to \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Data protection\&#34; and check whether a camera is listed in the sidebar under \&#34;Camera\&#34;. If no camera is displayed, then connect an external camera to your computer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;An external camera is not connected&lt;/b&gt;: Connect the external camera to your computer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The external camera is not switched on&lt;/b&gt;: Switch on the external camera if it has a switch.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is deactivated&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the device manager and check whether the displayed camera is deactivated under \&#34;Image devices\&#34;, \&#34;Camera\&#34; or \&#34;Integrated camera\&#34;. If so, right click on the camera and select \&#34;Activate\&#34;. (macOS) Restart the computer to reinstall the camera driver.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The driver of the camera is out of date&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the device manager and go to\&#34;Image devices\&#34;, \&#34;Camera\&#34; or \&#34;Integrated camera\&#34;. Right click on your camera and update the camera&#39;s driver. (macOS) Restart the computer to reinstall the camera driver.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked by an antivirus program&lt;/b&gt;: Allow your antivirus program or the antivirus extension in Google Chrome to use the camera or deactivate all antivirus programs for the duration of the exam.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other sources of error (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Check whether the camera is activated and working: &lt;a href=&#39;https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211130&#39;&gt;link to instructions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="camera_not_readable">Your camera cannot be recorded because it has no permission to do so. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Camera\&#34;. If the slider is on \&#34;Blocked\&#34;, then set it to \&#34;Ask before accessing (recommended)\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked for %system_name% in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Check whether there are links to WU websites under \&#34;Block\&#34;. Delete these websites from the list by clicking on the garbage can symbol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked for Google Chrome (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Go to \&#34;System Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy\&#34; and then in the sidebar on \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Activate the checkbox next to Google Chrome. Restart Google Chrome.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in the system settings for apps or desktop apps (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Apps\&#34; and \&#34;Desktop apps\&#34;. Check if apps and desktop apps are allowed to access your camera. If not, set the slider to \&#34;On\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in the system settings&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Check whether camera access is generally activated. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to activate general camera access. (macOS) Check that the camera is activated and working&lt;/b&gt;: link to instructions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera was switched off due to insufficient power supply (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Connect your computer to a power source. Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Check that camera access is still enabled for this device. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to reactivate camera access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="camera_permission_denied">Your camera cannot be recorded because it has no permission to do so. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Camera\&#34;. If the slider is on \&#34;Blocked\&#34;, then set it to \&#34;Ask before accessing (recommended)\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked for %system_name% in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Check whether there are links to WU websites under \&#34;Block\&#34;. Delete these websites from the list by clicking on the garbage can symbol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked for Google Chrome (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Go to \&#34;System Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy\&#34; and then in the sidebar on \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Activate the checkbox next to Google Chrome. Restart Google Chrome.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in the system settings for apps or desktop apps (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Apps\&#34; and \&#34;Desktop apps\&#34;. Check if apps and desktop apps are allowed to access your camera. If not, set the slider to \&#34;On\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in the system settings&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Check whether camera access is generally activated. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to activate general camera access. (macOS) Check that the camera is activated and working&lt;/b&gt;: link to instructions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera was switched off due to insufficient power supply (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Connect your computer to a power source. Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Camera\&#34;. Check that camera access is still enabled for this device. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to reactivate camera access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="check_again">Check again</msg>
  <msg key="community_help_text">If automated exam-supervision is activated, the system will create recordings of the participants and their screen.</msg>
  <msg key="desktop_cannot_be_recorded_because">Desktop cannot be recorded. Error is:</msg>
  <msg key="desktop_grabbing_not_supported">You are working with a browser that does not support the automated exam-supervision. Please use the latest version of Google &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.google.com/chrome/&#39;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;.</msg>
  <msg key="desktop_permission_denied">Your screen cannot be recorded because it has no permission to do so. Possible causes are: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The screen recording is blocked by an antivirus program&lt;/b&gt;: Allow your antivirus program or the antivirus protection extension in Google Chrome to record the screen or deactivate all antivirus programs for the duration of the exam.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The screen recording is blocked in the system settings (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Go to \&#34;System settings\&#34; | \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy\&#34; and then click on \&#34;Screen recording\&#34; in the sidebar. Activate the checkbox next to Google Chrome. Restart Google Chrome.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="display_surface_not_supported">You are working with a browser that does not support the automated exam-supervision. Please use the latest version of Google &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.google.com/chrome/&#39;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;.</msg>
  <msg key="Exam_mode">Exam mode</msg>
  <msg key="Exam_mode_message">&lt;h4&gt;Examination statement: Important information for taking online examinations&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;1) Participation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without exception, only students who are officially registered for the course and/or the examination on LPIS will be allowed to take the exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exam will only be graded if all 3 of the following conditions have been fulfilled:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;You have uploaded a photo that fulfills the necessary criteria to confirm your identity, if such an identification requirement was previously announced for the examination in question by the person responsible for the examination.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The automated online supervision functioned properly during the examination, if previously announced for this examination&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;You have confirmed that you have read and understood this examination statement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By confirming the examination statement, you also confirm receipt of the examination. If you have received the examination but not fulfilled the identity requirement and/or the automated online supervision did not function properly during the examination, the examination will be declared VOID and will count as an examination attempt. If you do not confirm the examination statement, you will not be given access to the exam. This means that the examination will not be graded and the examination attempt will not be counted.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;2) Technical requirements&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is your responsibility to ensure that you will not be disturbed during the examination and that all technical requirements (as previously announced) are fulfilled (see &#34;Information on this online examination&#34; and/or &#34;Technical checklist&#34; in your online exam environment). WU cannot guarantee a problem-free completion of the examination for every student working on their individual electronic device.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;3) Starting and terminating/interrupting the examination&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By confirming that you have read and understood this examination statement, you also confirm receipt of the examination, and the attempt will be counted. The exam will be graded and counted towards your total number of permissible examination attempts. This applies even if you terminate the exam prematurely or do not submit your completed exam.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are forced to terminate the exam prematurely or interrupt the exam due to technical difficulties (e.g. loss of your internet connection), please contact the person responsible for the examination without delay. To do that, please use the communication channel previously announced for that purpose by the person responsible for the examination. When reporting the termination/interruption of your exam, be sure to include the following information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Your student ID number&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Exact time of termination/interruption&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Screenshot of the error message, if applicable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are able to solve the problem and continue with the exam, please report this with the message &#34;Examination resumed.&#34; To be able to send such reports in the event of technical problems, it is recommended that you download the appropriate apps to your mobile devices before the start of the examination. In this way, you will for example be able to report the termination/interruption of the exam even if your Wi-Fi connection fails.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In cases where you report the termination/interruption of the exam due to technical problems beyond your control, as a general rule, the examination is not graded and the examination attempt not counted. If you would like to have your exam graded nonetheless, please contact the person responsible for the examination immediately after the exam and request that your exam be graded. The examination can only be graded if all the applicable requirements for grading are fulfilled (e.g. the automated online supervision worked properly, if applicable). Only those parts of the exam will be graded that were completed without any problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;4) Cheating and identity confirmation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any attempt to cheat on the exam (e.g. cell phone, consulting forbidden materials, consulting other people) will result in the exam being declared VOID and the examination attempt counted. You will also be blocked from re-registering to repeat the examination for a period of 4 months starting from the examination date. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having someone else take your exam for you can constitute a criminal offense. Such instances of cheating will be reported to the public prosecutor&#39;s office, without exception.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If announced in advance by the person responsible for the exam, automated online examination supervision will be conducted for the duration of the exam. This means that you and your screen will be monitored by camera and microphone (video and audio) throughout the exam, and the examiner will be able to see and hear the recordings. As soon as you start the exam, you will need to give your browser permission to access your screen, webcam, and microphone. Any attempts to manipulate the online exam supervision will be considered attempts at cheating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;5) Permissible aids&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When taking this examination, you may use only the aids explicitly listed or not explicitly forbidden in the information on this specific exam under &#34;Online Exam&#34; by the person responsible for the examination. As a rule, no one else may be present in the same room with you while you are working on the exam. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Acknowledgement of the information on receipt and completion of the examination
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I confirm that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I have read and understood the information given above on taking this written online examination&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I fulfill all the requirements for taking this examination&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I will complete the examination independently and without consulting any forbidden aids&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I have read and understood the information on this specific exam under &#34;Online examination&#34;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I accept receipt of this examination, i.e. I acknowledge that the exam will be graded and will count towards my total number of examination attempts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="Examination_Statement">Examination Statement</msg>
  <msg key="grant_access_to_camera_msg">If your browser prompts you to give access to the camera, please do so. Once permission has been granted, a preview image will appear. Please make sure your face is clearly visible in the picture before proceeding.</msg>
  <msg key="grant_access_to_camera_title">Grant access to your camera</msg>
  <msg key="grant_access_to_desktop_msg">You are being prompted to give access to your desktop. Please first select &#34;Your Entire Screen&#34; and grant the access thereafter by clicking the button &#34;Share&#34;. On success you should see a preview of your desktop on the page.</msg>
  <msg key="grant_access_to_desktop_title">Grant access to your desktop</msg>
  <msg key="grant_access_to_microphone_msg">If your browser prompts you to give access to the microphone, please do so. Once permission has been granted, an audiowave will be displayed to test your microphone. Please make sure your microphone is not muted and the audiowave is moving and reacts to your voice.</msg>
  <msg key="grant_access_to_microphone_title">Grant access to your microphone</msg>
  <msg key="microphone_cannot_be_recorded_because">Microphone cannot be recorded. Error is:</msg>
  <msg key="microphone_not_found">No microphone was recognized. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The active microphone is not selected in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Microphone\&#34; and select the correct microphone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;There is no internal microphone&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the control panel of your computer, go to \&#34;Sound\&#34; | \&#34;Input\&#34; and check that a microphone is listed. (macOS) Under \&#34;System Settings\&#34; go to \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy\&#34; and check whether a microphone is listed under \&#34;Microphone\&#34; in the sidebar. If no microphone is listed, connect an external microphone to your computer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The internal microphone is defect or not installed correctly&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the control panel of your computer, go to \&#34;Sound\&#34; | \&#34;Input\&#34; and test the microphone displayed there. Troubleshoot if necessary. (macOS) Restart the computer to reinstall the sound driver.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone driver is out of date&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the device manager and go to \&#34;Audioinputs and -outputs\&#34;. Right click on your microphone and update the microphone&#39;s driver. (macOS) Restart the computer to reinstall the sound driver.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The external microphone is not connected&lt;/b&gt;: Connect the external microphone to your computer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The external microphone is not switched on&lt;/b&gt;: Switch on the external microphone if it has aswitch.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="microphone_not_readable">Your microphone cannot be recorded because it has no permission to do so. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. If the slider is on \&#34;Blocked\&#34;, then set it to \&#34;Ask before accessing (recommended)\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked for %system_name% in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. Check whether there are links to WU websites under \&#34;Block\&#34;. Delete these websites from the list by clicking on the garbage can symbol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked for Google Chrome (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Go to \&#34;System Preferences\&#34; and \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy\&#34; and then on \&#34;Microphone\&#34; in the sidebar. Activate the checkbox next to Google Chrome. Restart Google Chrome.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked in the system settings for apps and desktop apps (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Apps\&#34; and \&#34;Desktop apps\&#34;. Check that apps and desktop apps can access your microphone. If not, then set the slider there to \&#34;On\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked in the system settings (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. Check that microphone access is enabled for this device. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to activate microphone access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone has been switched off to save power (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Connect your computer to a power source. Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. Check that microphone access is still enabled for this device. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to reactivate microphone access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="microphone_permission_denied">Your microphone cannot be recorded because it has no permission to do so. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. If the slider is on \&#34;Blocked\&#34;, then set it to \&#34;Ask before accessing (recommended)\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked for %system_name% in Google Chrome&lt;/b&gt;: In Google Chrome go to \&#34;Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy and security\&#34; | \&#34;Site Settings\&#34; | \&#34;Permissions\&#34; | \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. Check whether there are links to WU websites under \&#34;Block\&#34;. Delete these websites from the list by clicking on the garbage can symbol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked for Google Chrome (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Go to \&#34;System Preferences\&#34; and \&#34;Security\&#34; | \&#34;Privacy\&#34; and then on \&#34;Microphone\&#34; in the sidebar. Activate the checkbox next to Google Chrome. Restart Google Chrome.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked in the system settings for apps and desktop apps (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Apps\&#34; and \&#34;Desktop apps\&#34;. Check that apps and desktop apps can access your microphone. If not, then set the slider there to \&#34;On\&#34;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is blocked in the system settings (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. Check that microphone access is enabled for this device. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to activate microphone access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone has been switched off to save power (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Connect your computer to a power source. Open the system settings of your computer and go to \&#34;Microphone\&#34;. Check that microphone access is still enabled for this device. If not, go to \&#34;Change\&#34; to reactivate microphone access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="microphone_volume_is_too_low">The microphone&#39;s sound recording is insufficient. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The volume of the microphone is set too low&lt;/b&gt;: Turn up the input volume. (Windows) Open your computer&#39;s control panel and go to \&#34;Sound\&#34; | \&#34;Input\&#34; | \&#34;Device properties\&#34;. Adjust the volume here. (macOS) Click on \&#34;System Preferences\&#34; | \&#34;Sound\&#34; and open the \&#34;Input\&#34; tab.Adjust the input volume on your microphone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is muted&lt;/b&gt;: Unmute it. Check the corresponding keyboard commands and all hardware settings such as the mute function directly in the sound settings or on the microphone / headset itself.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="missing_stream_message">Online Supervision has ended. However, it is still activated for this exam. Please close Google Chrome to completely exit the exam environment. Alternatively, you can restart the automated online supervision: By clicking \&#34;OK\&#34;, you are re-entering the exam environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When reporting this issue, please mention the following message: </msg>
  <msg key="mobile_devices_are_unsupported">Mobile devices are unsupported.</msg>
  <msg key="OnlineExam">Online Exam</msg>
  <msg key="preview_help_text">If enabled, a preview of recorded input will be displayed to users during the online supervision session.</msg>
  <msg key="Proctoring">Automated exam-supervision</msg>
  <msg key="Record_audio">Record audio</msg>
  <msg key="Record_camera">Record camera</msg>
  <msg key="Record_desktop">Record desktop</msg>
  <msg key="recordings">Recordings</msg>
  <msg key="request_failed">Request to the server has failed. Retry in 10s...</msg>
  <msg key="request_timeout">Request to the server timed out. Retry in 10s...</msg>
  <msg key="user_photo">Photo</msg>
  <msg key="wizard_finish">Finish</msg>
  <msg key="wrong_display_surface_selected">The screen cannot be recorded because you selected the wrong screen area. Select \&#34;Your Entire Screen\&#34; by clicking on the screen and then on \&#34;Share\&#34;.</msg>
  <msg key="you_are_producing_black_pictures_from_camera">%system_name% shows that your camera is producing black or otherwise indiscernible pictures at the moment. This could invalidate your exam attempt! Please check the following: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is the camera obstructed?&lt;/b&gt; Uncover the camera lens.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is it too dark in the room?&lt;/b&gt; Turn on a light source or open the curtains.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Was the camera turned off to save power (Windows)?&lt;/b&gt; Connect your computer to a power source. Open the system settings of your computer and go to  \&#34;Camera \&#34;. Check whether camera access is still enabled for this device. If not, go to  \&#34;Change \&#34; to reactivate camera access.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other sources of error (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Check whether the camera is still activated and working: &lt;a href=&#39;https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211130&#39;&gt;link to instructions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="you_are_producing_black_pictures_from_camera_wizard">The image recording by the camera is insufficient. Possible causes are: &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is sending black images because the camera is obstructed&lt;/b&gt;: Free the camera lens.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is sending black images because it is too dark in the room&lt;/b&gt;: Switch on a light source or open the curtains.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera is blocked in the system settings for apps (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Open the system settings of your computer and go to  \&#34;Apps \&#34;. Check if apps are allowed to access your camera. If not, set the slider to  \&#34;On \&#34;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The camera was turned off to save power (Windows)&lt;/b&gt;: Connect your computer to a power source. Open the system settings of your computer and go to  \&#34;Camera \&#34;. Check whether camera access is still enabled for this device. If not, go to  \&#34;Change \&#34; to reactivate camera access.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Other sources of error (macOS)&lt;/b&gt;: Check whether the camera is still activated and working: &lt;a href=&#39;https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211130&#39;&gt;link to instructions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="you_are_producing_black_pictures_from_desktop">Important Note:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;System shows that your desktop is producing black or otherwise indiscernible pictures at the moment. This could invalidate your exam attempt!&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Please make sure that your device is plugged into a power cord and that you are not running on battery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
  <msg key="your_microphone_is_muted">Your microphone is muted. Possible causes are:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is muted in the software settings&lt;/b&gt;: Unmute it. (Windows) Open \&#34;Microphone Properties\&#34;. If the microphone is muted under \&#34;Level\&#34;, click on the loudspeaker symbol to unmute it. (macOS) Click on \&#34;System Preferences\&#34; | \&#34;Sound\&#34; and open the \&#34;Input\&#34; tab. Remove the check mark next to \&#34;Mute.\&#34;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;The microphone is deactivated&lt;/b&gt;: (Windows) Open the control panel of your computer and go to \&#34;Sound\&#34; | \&#34;Input\&#34; | \&#34;Manage audio devices\&#34;. Check if your microphone is listed under \&#34;Disabled\&#34;. If so, activate it by clicking on the microphone name. (macOS) Restart the computer to reinstall the camera driver.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</msg>
</message_catalog>
